bluetooth.com 2019-09-30

# Privacy | Bluetooth Technology Website

## We are committed to user privacy in our products and services.

This policy outlines our personal information-handling practices. Any contact information provided to us will be handled in accordance with this policy. This policy covers the Bluetooth SIG individual website. Bluetooth SIG encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all websites you visit.

### Use of Personal Information

Bluetooth SIG continually strives to protect the information you share with us. Access to personal member information is limited to specific individuals, employees, and agents of Bluetooth SIG. Bluetooth SIG will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties. Bluetooth SIG may disclose personal information to third parties to complete a transaction you have requested, as part of the terms and conditions for a particular service, or when we otherwise have your consent to do so.

### Linked Websites

Bluetooth SIG provides links to third party sites. Since Bluetooth SIG does not control these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these (and all) third party sites.

### Cookies

The Bluetooth SIG website uses cookies. Cookies help provide a better user experience by measuring which website areas are of greatest interest. Bluetooth SIG also uses cookies when an individual registers for a web application. In this situation, a cookie stores useful information that enables the website to remember that individual user. Bluetooth SIG can only access cookies from the websites it controls.

If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of our websites. Please be aware, however, that some websites will not allow you to complete certain activities if cookies are disabled.

The Bluetooth SIG website may display advertisements from third parties. Third party ad-serving companies control which ads are shown. These ad-serving companies may use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information from website visitors. Advertisers use this information to target the ads and measure their impact.
